[
    {
        "id": "256cf4b7-34aa-473f-b5ac-674f9cfe6ce0",
        "user_created": "4770f9b3-4f25-4ef8-9a3e-0956eb688be5",
        "date_created": "2023-12-05T09:06:01.865Z",
        "user_updated": null,
        "date_updated": null,
        "answers": [
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "742cb85f-0331-4990-a03d-a44d3ae02538",
                    "user_created": "4770f9b3-4f25-4ef8-9a3e-0956eb688be5",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T09:06:01.871Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "7fa35070-16eb-41b6-9fa1-2e9ee50c8f9f",
                    "response": ["Bloating or feeling bloated"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "84498c4f-f19d-418c-a80e-360a64d662df",
                    "user_created": "4770f9b3-4f25-4ef8-9a3e-0956eb688be5",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T09:06:01.896Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "b3055c80-24b4-43f8-a52a-a9ae56891e04",
                    "response": ["Less than a week ago"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "5104be27-478f-4ee8-8458-c6870c81e95b",
                    "user_created": "4770f9b3-4f25-4ef8-9a3e-0956eb688be5",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T09:06:01.935Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "695c71ec-3dce-4bc2-81a9-f08bc0d42745",
                    "response": ["Gastritis","SIBO"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "1686a19e-bdb9-4284-8748-960553171a77",
                    "user_created": "4770f9b3-4f25-4ef8-9a3e-0956eb688be5",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T09:06:01.962Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "9a76d63a-3ba2-468a-a336-b07a2731b620",
                    "response": ["Moderate"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "c2645c8d-34f6-4cdc-b3c8-4d8454f7f52c",
                    "user_created": "4770f9b3-4f25-4ef8-9a3e-0956eb688be5",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T09:06:01.990Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "bb322edf-830a-439b-a067-d134dc1f8981",
                    "response": ["Antipasmodics","Cognitive Behavioural Therapy"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "42ae9b81-db44-49c9-bd7e-4c4c0a8360e2",
                    "user_created": "4770f9b3-4f25-4ef8-9a3e-0956eb688be5",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T09:06:02.030Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "bf46aafd-3750-4358-9dbf-9a3ab510cc37",
                    "response": ["Fractose","Gluten/Grains or Cereals"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "23c06014-57b6-46d3-821e-0116f49c569c",
                    "user_created": "4770f9b3-4f25-4ef8-9a3e-0956eb688be5",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T09:06:02.051Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "8dbad511-37f1-4371-9033-a33c253d3873",
                    "response": ["Test Meds 1 x 2"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "55ff413d-ca0d-4c57-aa65-eed6035a2232",
                    "user_created": "4770f9b3-4f25-4ef8-9a3e-0956eb688be5",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T09:06:02.080Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "60bdc8d9-41fc-4dc4-9d7d-273deebebcbe",
                    "response": ["Test Condition 1 few days back"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "4fe4d3d4-812d-4470-8670-c012316bfa50",
                    "user_created": "4770f9b3-4f25-4ef8-9a3e-0956eb688be5",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T09:06:02.107Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "936dd879-34d1-469e-bfb4-f5935a74c370",
                    "response": ["Not very severe"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "10da50d6-3d69-45b4-bd95-7a2725cc8f5d",
                    "user_created": "4770f9b3-4f25-4ef8-9a3e-0956eb688be5",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T09:06:02.140Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "da18f429-b36e-41fc-bce9-e5fca2b926fe",
                    "response": ["2"]
                }
            }
        ],
        "form": {
            "id": "cd76c5a0-775a-44fe-adf4-6d78c1ecdd3a",
            "status": "published",
            "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
            "date_created": "2023-10-06T22:57:46.256Z",
            "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
            "date_updated": "2023-11-22T15:30:34.187Z",
            "name": "App Form",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "7fa35070-16eb-41b6-9fa1-2e9ee50c8f9f",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T07:15:37.354Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.342Z",
                        "question": "What is the main symptom bringing you here?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "1",
                        "choices": [
                            7,
                            8,
                            9,
                            10,
                            11,
                            12
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "b3055c80-24b4-43f8-a52a-a9ae56891e04",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T07:56:30.930Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.372Z",
                        "question": "When did your symptoms first start?",
                        "type": "singlechoice",
                        "key": "2",
                        "choices": [
                            13,
                            14,
                            15,
                            16
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "695c71ec-3dce-4bc2-81a9-f08bc0d42745",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T07:58:59.831Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.405Z",
                        "question": "Which of these conditions are you suffering from?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "3",
                        "choices": [
                            17,
                            18,
                            19,
                            20,
                            21,
                            22,
                            23,
                            24,
                            35
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "9a76d63a-3ba2-468a-a336-b07a2731b620",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:37:16.946Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "How strongly are your symptoms are limiting your daily lifestyle?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "4",
                        "choices": [
                            25,
                            26,
                            27,
                            28,
                            29
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "bb322edf-830a-439b-a067-d134dc1f8981",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.206Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-22T15:30:34.197Z",
                        "question": "What treatments have you tried before?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "5",
                        "choices": [
                            30,
                            31,
                            32,
                            33,
                            34,
                            88
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "bf46aafd-3750-4358-9dbf-9a3ab510cc37",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:39:55.855Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "Which food sensitives do you have?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "6",
                        "choices": [
                            36,
                            37,
                            38,
                            39,
                            40,
                            41,
                            42,
                            43,
                            44,
                            45
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "8dbad511-37f1-4371-9033-a33c253d3873",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.166Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": " List all your current medications with dosage?",
                        "type": "text",
                        "key": "7",
                        "choices": []
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "60bdc8d9-41fc-4dc4-9d7d-273deebebcbe",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.190Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "List pre-existing conditions?",
                        "type": "text",
                        "key": "7",
                        "choices": []
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "936dd879-34d1-469e-bfb4-f5935a74c370",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.209Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "What is your current bloating condition?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "8",
                        "choices": [
                            46,
                            47,
                            48,
                            49
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "da18f429-b36e-41fc-bce9-e5fca2b926fe",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.331Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "What is your current stool frequency in a day?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "8",
                        "choices": [
                            50,
                            51,
                            52,
                            53,
                            54,
                            55,
                            56,
                            57,
                            58,
                            59
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "0d8be11d-7ee2-40e6-817a-4c9ce5712e08",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:43:25.117Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "What is your current abdominal pain?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "8",
                        "choices": [
                            60,
                            61,
                            62,
                            63
                        ]
                    }
                }
            ]
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "479ce0d3-6344-47e4-8e67-ddfca639c8b9",
        "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
        "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.588Z",
        "user_updated": null,
        "date_updated": null,
        "answers": [
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "c74f00f0-64d2-4eff-8798-6078cb822ea1",
                    "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.594Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "7fa35070-16eb-41b6-9fa1-2e9ee50c8f9f",
                    "response": ["Bloating or feeling bloated","Diarrhea"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "a05da9d4-f24e-4a23-8097-3183954e99f7",
                    "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.615Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "b3055c80-24b4-43f8-a52a-a9ae56891e04",
                    "response": ["Less than a week ago"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "d00c16fc-2766-4d9e-95c6-fb5d6534502a",
                    "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.644Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "695c71ec-3dce-4bc2-81a9-f08bc0d42745",
                    "response": ["SIBO","Gastritis","Functional Dyspepsia"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "d1afcd5c-0d6b-4115-8a66-b53d3504ecb4",
                    "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.665Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "9a76d63a-3ba2-468a-a336-b07a2731b620",
                    "response": ["Not very severe"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "4b200ce8-b44c-48da-959d-84c7b265f012",
                    "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.694Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "bb322edf-830a-439b-a067-d134dc1f8981",
                    "response": ["Diet","Antipasmodics"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "d62a77b3-a47f-4b54-9de2-06feba53ac53",
                    "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.713Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "bf46aafd-3750-4358-9dbf-9a3ab510cc37",
                    "response": [" Garlic/Onion","Gluten/Grains or Cereals","Beans","Soy"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "6fe3561f-9f98-4f05-8cbb-5f14bc85288c",
                    "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.734Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "8dbad511-37f1-4371-9033-a33c253d3873",
                    "response": ["no "]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "37f5c9df-bc60-40e7-a107-2d0ef5878de9",
                    "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.762Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "60bdc8d9-41fc-4dc4-9d7d-273deebebcbe",
                    "response": ["no "]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "488b7340-efbc-4747-93e9-2ca4fcc94cf8",
                    "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.783Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "936dd879-34d1-469e-bfb4-f5935a74c370",
                    "response": ["Not very severe"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "29e6563e-dfd8-48b3-8ead-dc0b484ba4bd",
                    "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.803Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "da18f429-b36e-41fc-bce9-e5fca2b926fe",
                    "response": ["4"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "aa233634-5cfc-463b-9c8f-70aa119df7bb",
                    "user_created": "d824e85f-6da1-497a-aa0d-8b25efd6150f",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-18T05:12:50.823Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "0d8be11d-7ee2-40e6-817a-4c9ce5712e08",
                    "response": ["Noticeable discomfort"]
                }
            }
        ],
        "form": {
            "id": "cd76c5a0-775a-44fe-adf4-6d78c1ecdd3a",
            "status": "published",
            "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
            "date_created": "2023-10-06T22:57:46.256Z",
            "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
            "date_updated": "2023-11-22T15:30:34.187Z",
            "name": "App Form",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "7fa35070-16eb-41b6-9fa1-2e9ee50c8f9f",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T07:15:37.354Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.342Z",
                        "question": "What is the main symptom bringing you here?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "1",
                        "choices": [
                            7,
                            8,
                            9,
                            10,
                            11,
                            12
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "b3055c80-24b4-43f8-a52a-a9ae56891e04",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T07:56:30.930Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.372Z",
                        "question": "When did your symptoms first start?",
                        "type": "singlechoice",
                        "key": "2",
                        "choices": [
                            13,
                            14,
                            15,
                            16
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "695c71ec-3dce-4bc2-81a9-f08bc0d42745",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T07:58:59.831Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.405Z",
                        "question": "Which of these conditions are you suffering from?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "3",
                        "choices": [
                            17,
                            18,
                            19,
                            20,
                            21,
                            22,
                            23,
                            24,
                            35
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "9a76d63a-3ba2-468a-a336-b07a2731b620",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:37:16.946Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "How strongly are your symptoms are limiting your daily lifestyle?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "4",
                        "choices": [
                            25,
                            26,
                            27,
                            28,
                            29
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "bb322edf-830a-439b-a067-d134dc1f8981",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.206Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-22T15:30:34.197Z",
                        "question": "What treatments have you tried before?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "5",
                        "choices": [
                            30,
                            31,
                            32,
                            33,
                            34,
                            88
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "bf46aafd-3750-4358-9dbf-9a3ab510cc37",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:39:55.855Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "Which food sensitives do you have?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "6",
                        "choices": [
                            36,
                            37,
                            38,
                            39,
                            40,
                            41,
                            42,
                            43,
                            44,
                            45
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "8dbad511-37f1-4371-9033-a33c253d3873",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.166Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": " List all your current medications with dosage?",
                        "type": "text",
                        "key": "7",
                        "choices": []
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "60bdc8d9-41fc-4dc4-9d7d-273deebebcbe",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.190Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "List pre-existing conditions?",
                        "type": "text",
                        "key": "7",
                        "choices": []
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "936dd879-34d1-469e-bfb4-f5935a74c370",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.209Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "What is your current bloating condition?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "8",
                        "choices": [
                            46,
                            47,
                            48,
                            49
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "da18f429-b36e-41fc-bce9-e5fca2b926fe",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.331Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "What is your current stool frequency in a day?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "8",
                        "choices": [
                            50,
                            51,
                            52,
                            53,
                            54,
                            55,
                            56,
                            57,
                            58,
                            59
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "0d8be11d-7ee2-40e6-817a-4c9ce5712e08",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:43:25.117Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "What is your current abdominal pain?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "8",
                        "choices": [
                            60,
                            61,
                            62,
                            63
                        ]
                    }
                }
            ]
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "bf495bb4-0f42-4fc8-9185-912be3b3f090",
        "user_created": "dd38322a-35ed-4681-b46e-3e8a803dc17b",
        "date_created": "2023-12-05T07:37:01.744Z",
        "user_updated": null,
        "date_updated": null,
        "answers": [
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "87cd783d-f792-499f-b651-5a9beb414b34",
                    "user_created": "dd38322a-35ed-4681-b46e-3e8a803dc17b",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T07:37:01.752Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "7fa35070-16eb-41b6-9fa1-2e9ee50c8f9f",
                    "response": ["Bloating or feeling bloated","Constipated"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "849a9667-6908-4dfd-9b2b-494aaa26c146",
                    "user_created": "dd38322a-35ed-4681-b46e-3e8a803dc17b",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T07:37:01.774Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "b3055c80-24b4-43f8-a52a-a9ae56891e04",
                    "response": ["A few months"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "6200f112-3ddc-45ff-838b-688616a74aae",
                    "user_created": "dd38322a-35ed-4681-b46e-3e8a803dc17b",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T07:37:01.794Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "9a76d63a-3ba2-468a-a336-b07a2731b620",
                    "response": ["Not very severe"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "95f0d691-c471-4a0f-af5b-c7057891a7bf",
                    "user_created": "dd38322a-35ed-4681-b46e-3e8a803dc17b",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T07:37:01.817Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "bf46aafd-3750-4358-9dbf-9a3ab510cc37",
                    "response": ["Fractose","Beans","Others","Peanuts"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "dff358f6-2474-4c27-b7da-682c0f440961",
                    "user_created": "dd38322a-35ed-4681-b46e-3e8a803dc17b",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T07:37:01.843Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "695c71ec-3dce-4bc2-81a9-f08bc0d42745",
                    "response": ["None"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "20c9eb02-b063-4c84-80c0-b1a3917d6b97",
                    "user_created": "dd38322a-35ed-4681-b46e-3e8a803dc17b",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T07:37:01.874Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "bb322edf-830a-439b-a067-d134dc1f8981",
                    "response": ["Cognitive Behavioural Therapy"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "159c1e69-1a74-49a7-a6d5-4d104402dd32",
                    "user_created": "dd38322a-35ed-4681-b46e-3e8a803dc17b",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T07:37:01.895Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "60bdc8d9-41fc-4dc4-9d7d-273deebebcbe",
                    "response": ["hjyfgyhj"]
                }
            },
            {
                "form_answers_id": {
                    "id": "39c5ff19-f765-4228-b5d5-c80c42a51f68",
                    "user_created": "dd38322a-35ed-4681-b46e-3e8a803dc17b",
                    "date_created": "2023-12-05T07:37:01.922Z",
                    "user_updated": null,
                    "date_updated": null,
                    "question": "8dbad511-37f1-4371-9033-a33c253d3873",
                    "response": ["hjbkjkh"]
                }
            }
        ],
        "form": {
            "id": "cd76c5a0-775a-44fe-adf4-6d78c1ecdd3a",
            "status": "published",
            "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
            "date_created": "2023-10-06T22:57:46.256Z",
            "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
            "date_updated": "2023-11-22T15:30:34.187Z",
            "name": "App Form",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "7fa35070-16eb-41b6-9fa1-2e9ee50c8f9f",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T07:15:37.354Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.342Z",
                        "question": "What is the main symptom bringing you here?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "1",
                        "choices": [
                            7,
                            8,
                            9,
                            10,
                            11,
                            12
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "b3055c80-24b4-43f8-a52a-a9ae56891e04",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T07:56:30.930Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.372Z",
                        "question": "When did your symptoms first start?",
                        "type": "singlechoice",
                        "key": "2",
                        "choices": [
                            13,
                            14,
                            15,
                            16
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "695c71ec-3dce-4bc2-81a9-f08bc0d42745",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T07:58:59.831Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.405Z",
                        "question": "Which of these conditions are you suffering from?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "3",
                        "choices": [
                            17,
                            18,
                            19,
                            20,
                            21,
                            22,
                            23,
                            24,
                            35
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "9a76d63a-3ba2-468a-a336-b07a2731b620",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:37:16.946Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "How strongly are your symptoms are limiting your daily lifestyle?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "4",
                        "choices": [
                            25,
                            26,
                            27,
                            28,
                            29
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "bb322edf-830a-439b-a067-d134dc1f8981",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:37:17.206Z",
                        "user_updated": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_updated": "2023-11-22T15:30:34.197Z",
                        "question": "What treatments have you tried before?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "5",
                        "choices": [
                            30,
                            31,
                            32,
                            33,
                            34,
                            88
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "bf46aafd-3750-4358-9dbf-9a3ab510cc37",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:39:55.855Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "Which food sensitives do you have?",
                        "type": "multichoice",
                        "key": "6",
                        "choices": [
                            36,
                            37,
                            38,
                            39,
                            40,
                            41,
                            42,
                            43,
                            44,
                            45
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "8dbad511-37f1-4371-9033-a33c253d3873",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.166Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": " List all your current medications with dosage?",
                        "type": "text",
                        "key": "7",
                        "choices": []
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "60bdc8d9-41fc-4dc4-9d7d-273deebebcbe",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.190Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "List pre-existing conditions?",
                        "type": "text",
                        "key": "7",
                        "choices": []
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "936dd879-34d1-469e-bfb4-f5935a74c370",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.209Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "What is your current bloating condition?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "8",
                        "choices": [
                            46,
                            47,
                            48,
                            49
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "da18f429-b36e-41fc-bce9-e5fca2b926fe",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:42:25.331Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "What is your current stool frequency in a day?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "8",
                        "choices": [
                            50,
                            51,
                            52,
                            53,
                            54,
                            55,
                            56,
                            57,
                            58,
                            59
                        ]
                    }
                },
                {
                    "form_question_id": {
                        "id": "0d8be11d-7ee2-40e6-817a-4c9ce5712e08",
                        "user_created": "dfd27599-42d0-4fe0-9c7d-29902e9b4aa2",
                        "date_created": "2023-11-14T08:43:25.117Z",
                        "user_updated": null,
                        "date_updated": null,
                        "question": "What is your current abdominal pain?",
                        "type": "slider",
                        "key": "8",
                        "choices": [
                            60,
                            61,
                            62,
                            63
                        ]
                    }
                }
            ]
        }
    }
]